



+55 (31) 98849-6756



juliospn@gmail.com



julio-spnascimento

# Extra education Alura Online Training

HTML CSS

Frontend

JavaScrpit for Backend

Vue.js

WebFlow

Wordpress

**Business Agility** 

# Languages

Portuguese (Native) English (Advanced)

# Extracurricular

Crossfit, sports and bodybuilding Economic philosophy and Bitcoin

#### ARE THE MEANS THAT JUSTIFY THE ENDS

Hi! My name is Julio and I'm 32 years old. I am an observant professional with varied skills (a true nexialist!), I have a solid purpose and ambition to impact the world with small daily steps. I like to think counterintuitively when faced with challenging problems. I am looking for a company with the same ideals to be able to contribute to the journey and absorb good experiences.

#### **PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE**

#### Pedivela 175

2020 - 2021

Bike shop assistant

- Product registration and transition to using a software for inventory control
- o Online sales support.
- · Social media management.
- E-commerce website development.

### Geolurb

2019 - 2020

Engineering intern

- Assistance in preparing reports and content for lectures.
- Geotechnical monitoring of works.

## **ACADEMIC EDUCATION**

## **Federal University of Ouro Preto**

2014 - 2019

Civil Engineering Graduate